Damon Elrod

damonelrod@gmail.com | (916) 474-1643 | Granite Bay Ca, 95746

Summary

Currently seeking an entry level position in the IT and/or Cybersecurity fields. I am well versed in customer service, personal communication, training, and supervision. I also bring a strong level of experience and accountability working in team-oriented, collaborative environments. I am CompTIA A+ certified and in progress towards the Network+ certification.

As a 7 year competitive rower at both the highschool and collegiate levels, I am well acquainted with tough work in a teamwork driven environment. I am looking forward to bringing my skills and 'get after it' attitude to my next opportunity.

Core Competencies

Customer Service | Conflict Resolution | Training & Instruction | Leadership & Supervision

Technical Proficiencies

MS Windows | MS Office | Google Workspace / GSuite (Docs | Sheets | Slides | Forms)
Hardware Troubleshooting | Software Troubleshooting

Experience

SAC State ASI Aquatic Center. Gold River Ca Assistant Rowing Coach

SEP 2019 - PRESENT

- Supervision and training of athletes and staff
- Program development and implementation
- Data metrics and analysis
- Key Performance Indicator (KPI) tracking and reporting
- Equipment maintenance
- Communications management internal & external program outreach / recruitment
- Accountable for safety of athletes while they practice, operation of motor boats on public waterways, personal interaction with other coaches, athletes, and parents.

Peet's Coffee and Tea. Granite Bay Ca

JAN 2020 - PRESENT

Certified Barista

- Customer service & cash handling
- Inventory management
- Onsite technical support

Round Table Pizza, Folsom Ca

JUN 2017 - SEP 2017 | JUN 2018 - SEP 2018

Delivery Driver

- Customer service
- Food delivery
- Account reconciliation

Rex Moore, Sacramento Ca

JUN 2015 - SEP 2015

Manufacturer

- Warehouseman
- Electrical assembly
- Team based operations

Other Relevant Experience

Co-Captain for UCSB Varsity Crew Team

SEP 2018 - JUN 2019

- Scheduling management
- Conflict resolution
- Management & supervision
- Team leadership
 Accountability & responsibility for team logistics, safety, and conduct.

Education

University of California Santa Barbara, Goleta Ca

Bachelor's degree, Chemistry

Certifications

- CompTIA A+
- CompTIA Network+ (in progress)